{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/51622905","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622905","name":"Detroit Mini Donut","address":"206 Grand River E. Ste 1D","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Karen Hudson/Detroit Mini Donu","licenseNumber":"238158","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.04664,42.33550","geojson":{"id":"51622905","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.046642564,42.335503193]},"properties":{"name":"Detroit Mini Donut","owner":"Karen Hudson/Detroit Mini Donu","address":"206 Grand River E. Ste 1D","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"238158","establishmentid":"51622905","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":"2022-05-25"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51623358","name":"I Love You Juicery","address":"206 Grand River E.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5368","name":"Chubby Duck Detroit","address":"208 Grand River E.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5337","name":"I Luv Cheese","address":"1368  Broadway","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4890","name":"Cafe Al Karar","address":"1368 Broadway","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2716","name":"Harmonie Way","address":"218 Grand River E.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4906","name":"Jose's Tacos, LLC","address":"218 Grand River E.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3913","name":"Al's Paradise Cafe, LLC","address":"218  Grand River","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51623950","name":"Detroit Mini Donut ( Oakland)","address":"214 Grand River E.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2621","name":"Coaches Corner of Detroit","address":"1465 Centre","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4643","name":"Zante LLC DBA Paris Bar","address":"1344-46 Broadway","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"61972","inspectionDate":"2023-03-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Single-service/use items","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the Counter(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2023-03-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING ROOM","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING ROOM","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING ROOM","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"59907","inspectionDate":"2022-08-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"and the Dishwashing room","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-08-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"57394","inspectionDate":"2022-02-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"and the Dishwashing room","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-02-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"55940","inspectionDate":"2021-09-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"54265","inspectionDate":"2021-02-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"BACK ROOM","subLocation":"At the Three compartment sink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-02-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"52435","inspectionDate":"2020-08-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.19","violationDescription":"Toilet room doors shall be kept closed except during cleaning and maintenance operations.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Door","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (FRONT AREA)","subLocation":"At the door(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"50570","inspectionDate":"2020-01-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"MFL289.4119","violationDescription":"Sec. 4119. (1) Except as otherwise provided in subsection (2), a person licensed as a food establishment under this chapter shall keep a copy of the current license or temporary license furnished by the department posted and exposed in a conspicuous place for public inspection. A conspicuous place is the principal place where food business is transacted.  (2) In the case of vending machines, the name and address and telephone number of the current vending machine location operator shall be conspicuously displayed on each vending machine.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food Service License","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not displayed","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.19","violationDescription":"Toilet room doors shall be kept closed except during cleaning and maintenance operations.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Door","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Propped open","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"In the front","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"48619","inspectionDate":"2019-08-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Restroom(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"48281","inspectionDate":"2019-07-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622905"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}